thinkwave.com 2001-12-02

# ThinkWave

|  |   
---  
  
| Homepage  
  
| How ThinkWave works  
  
| Why use ThinkWave  
  
| What users are saying  
| Products and Services  
  
| FAQ  
  
| Demo  
  
| Help  
|   
  
|    

## Overview

ThinkWave, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our members. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our service. The policy may be updated occasionally so please check back periodically.

To ensure our members’ privacy and the security of their information, ThinkWave, Inc. has taken the following precautions:

  * ThinkWave, Inc. uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to enhance the privacy of grades and class results transmitted online. 
  * We will never sell or share any personal information with any person or organization outside of ThinkWave, Inc. 
  * Personally identifiable information (such as full name, phone number, or birthday) is not displayed on ThinkWave.com. 
  * ThinkWave is compliant with Child’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) regulations. 
  * ThinkWave accounts are password-protected.*

(*Members are responsible for maintaining the security of passwords.)

## Privacy

ThinkWave, Inc. has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

ThinkWave, Inc. uses your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

ThinkWave, Inc. uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies do not personally identify users, but they do identify a user’s computer. ThinkWave, Inc. generally uses cookies to:

    1. personalize your view on ThinkWave.com; 
    2. deliver content and advertisements specific to your interests; 
    3. estimate audience size; and 
    4. measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of the website you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. 

Our site's registration form may ask users to give us contact information such as name and email address and demographic information such as zip code, age, or income level. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact visitors when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor visitors' experiences at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.  Personal information will not be shared with advertisers. ThinkWave may provide personal information to third parties, including but not limited to law enforcement agencies, if required to do so by law or court order.

This site contains links to other sites. While we certainly try not to link to any sites that contain unsuitable or inappropriate material, ThinkWave, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any sites but our own.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors’ contact information such as their email address and financial information such as their account or credit card numbers. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below.) Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

We will use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use **cookies** in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here:  [www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm).

## Security

**ThinkWave, Inc. has strict security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.**

ThinkWave, Inc. uses individual password-protected accounts and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to enhance the privacy of grades and class results transmitted online.

ThinkWave accounts are all password-protected so that only authorized members are allowed to access or view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. ThinkWave does not ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. 

## Personal Information

ThinkWave, Inc. is committed to safeguarding personal information online. Personally identifiable information such as full names, addresses, phone numbers and e-mail addresses are not displayed on ThinkWave.com. ThinkWave Educator publishes only students' classroom data onto from ThinkWave Educator to ThinkWave.com. This includes classes, assignments, grades and attendance. This information is accessible only by individual parent and student ThinkWave ID's and passwords.

## Teachers' Guidelines

ThinkWave, Inc. is committed to safeguarding personal information online. Personally identifiable information such as full names, addresses, phone numbers and e-mail addresses are not displayed on ThinkWave.com. ThinkWave Educator publishes only students' classroom data onto from ThinkWave Educator to ThinkWave.com. This includes classes, assignments, grades and attendance. This information is accessible only by individual parent and student ThinkWave ID's and passwords.

## Children's Guidelines (under 13)

ThinkWave is in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and with Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) _Self-Regulatory Guidelines for Children's Advertising_.

We take the following measures to protect the security and privacy of children:

  * We do NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. 
  * We do NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. 
  * We do NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information without prior parental consent. 
  * We do NOT give the ability to publicly post personally identifiable contact information to ThinkWave.com. 
  * We do NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor on our software request page. Please **contact ThinkWave, Inc**. if you would like to:

  * remove information from our database to not receive future communications; 
  * change and modify information previously provided; or 
  * ask questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, please contact ThinkWave, Inc. at: ThinkWave/475 Gate Five Road/Suite 120/Sausalito, CA 94965 or via email at [privacy@thinkwave.com](mailto:privacy@thinkwave.com).

|
